I just want to address this before I get up and go do my show of views from Amanda Land
that I do every week for free.
Anyone who is saying that me going on Jubilee was a bad idea because we don't need that
right now.
You all are the same ilk of people who said to all of the Dr. Martin Luther King followers,
Freedom Writers, SNCC, etc.
You're stirring up trouble.
You are the same people who consider challenging political candidates to be divisive and somehow
counterintuitive to actually getting representation from people who are supposed to be representing
you.
Yes, I am being condescending right now.
You are the same people who want to pretend that there hasn't been a deep immersion of
indoctrination within the black community, even though it's staring you in the face in
the episode, because somehow you feel like if you show that, then it will expose that there's
been divide and conquer.
Baby, there has been divide and conquer.
And the failure to want to address that head on is the same type of crap that keeps us from
actually being a catalyst for change.
You are cowards.
You want to run from the difficult truths.
And that's the same reason why you are in a relationship that actually you hate waking up to
every day.
Side note, couples therapy is not going to fix it if you all are not going to individual
therapy yourselves.
Second, if you are talking about AIPAC, but you're not loudly yelling for a free Palestine,
then you're just pretending.
Being consistent in your principles and morals does not have to be anomalous.
Being critical of politicians, of mainstream media, of the people in your circle who are not showing
up in principles and values that actually can lead to change is not being judgmental.
It's actually being responsible.
Have a good day.